calendardate.com 2019-09-01

# Privacy Policy - Calendar Date

#### Privacy Policy

CalendarDate.com values and is committed to privacy. While you visit the Site, the Site may monitor traffic, statistics and collect and gather information. This is intended to better gauge Site User interests, to streamline the experience, and to achieve a more efficient management of the Site in order to make it more useful.

#### Personal Information

We do collect your IP address along with other web server data including pages visited and web browsing behavior while on the website. All information collected is used only for our own internal use and is never shared with outside sources. We do use third party solutions like Google Analytics, Ad networks, Google Site Search, and Social Media to help us provide a better user experience and serve relevant ads with each party having its own privacy policy.

#### Google Analytics

Used to track how users utilize our website and provide reports for us to better understand user engagement with the site. Please access [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us "Google Privacy Policy") for more information on what information they gather and how it is stored.

#### Ad Networks

Ad networks like Google Adsense are used on the site to keep the website usage free of charge. Ad networks use Cookies (see below “Cookies) to serve relevant ads based on past websites the user has visited. Users can gain more control of their ads by signing into their Google Account and by visiting [Ad Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated "Google Ad Settings") to adjust their ad topic preferences. You may also opt out of specific vendor ad networks uses of cookies by visiting [Opt Out - About Ads](http://optout.aboutads.info/ "Opt out Ads"). In the European Union Ads are not personalized therefore cookies used only contain frequency capping, and aggregated ad reporting information. Users in the European Union can find more information available at [Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ "Online Choices"). For details on how Google uses cookies on their ad networks visit [Google Advertising Cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=us "Google Advertising Cookies Privacy Policy").

#### Google Site Search

The site search function is powered by Google Search with their privacy policy found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us "Google Privacy Policy").

#### Social Media 

Facebook and Twitter social media provide code for us to use on our website that puts a cookie on the users computer when the social media button is clicked on. Please see [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php "Facebook Privacy Policy"), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/en/privacy "Twitter Privacy Policy") individual privacy policies for more information about what they do with user personal data.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer. We use cookies to make the users experience better while browsing the web. Information like past webpages visited, items placed in shopping cart, etc. are all stored in the small text file called a cookie. To manage or disable cookies on your browser, see your browser options or the browsers' website for more information.

As a user of CalendarDate.com you agree and give consent for the Website and its third party partners to use your personal data in accordance with their respective privacy policies. If you do not agree with said privacy policies please do not use this website and its services.

This privacy policy was last updated on May 14, 2018.

Please feel free to [Contact Us](https://www.calendardate.com/supportcont.htm "Contact Us") regarding any questions or concerns you may have regarding our Privacy Policy.
